(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T05:28:57.931120",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
MAKE IT, BREAK IT - FLOW GLOW 3D LIVE
Yeah,
This is FLOW GLOW from hololive device
お待たせしました
Sorry to keep you waiting!
FLOW GLOW 3Dお披露目ライブ
FLOW GLOW 3D Debut Live!
Make it!
Break it up!
楽しむ準備できてますか！？
Are you ready to have some fun?!
搭載V8エンジン
Packin' a V8 engine
第7感持ってる原人
And a seventh sense for things
Rockするこの世界と全人類
Rocking this world and all humanity
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
With us five, the game is changing
鳴る4輪発射セヨ
Four wheels firing off
皆さんサンキューサランヘヨ
Thank you all, sarang hae yo
操る2台のturntable
Spinning two turntables
獲る1番ここground 0
Becoming number one, starting here ground 0
リスク超えて挑戦
Face the risks and challenge it
チャンスもセットだ当然
Chance is set too, naturally
登り上げる頂点
Climbing to the peak
座布団積んでる笑点
Piling up zabuton for laughs
乗り込むFG ROADSTER
Riding into the FG ROADSTER
特殊部隊集合能力者
Special unit of espers gathered
この歴史に名を刻む彫刻家
Sculptors carving our names in history
ぶっちぎりで置き去り後続車
Leaving trailing cars in the dust
今高速でぶっちぎっていく大気圏
Speeding through the stratosphere
エンジンからジェットの炎揺れてる怪気炎
Jet flames flickering from the engine
眼下に広がる大地を超えていく回帰線
Crossing the tropics below us
バックミラーにbig blueが写っているIBM
Big blue reflected in the rearview, IBM
打ち上げ台から飛んでいく宇宙世代
Taking off from the launch pad, our generation
この燃料朽ち果てないです | en: This fuel will never burn out
This fuel will never burn out
銀河で寿司食べたい
We wanna eat sushi in a galaxy
見えてるでかいビジョン
We can see a massive vision
燃えてるメンバー一同
All of us members are burning
ただいま現在進行形
Right now, present continuous
超えてく世界規模
Going above and beyond global scale
叶えるはずだwon't stop
Dreams come true, we won't stop
心臓がモンスター
Our hearts are a monster
aliens turn it up
FG party hard
光るtesla roadster
Blingin' Tesla roadster
heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Awakening our instincts
青い炎 (woo! woo!)
Blue flames (woo! woo!)
BFF let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Prisoners to nothing, from naught to space
走るFG ROADSTER
Speeding the FG ROADSTER
鳴るbooster
Hitting that booster
FLOW GLOW the space to be
いまchase me
Now chase me
ターボ付きスーパーカー
A turbocharged supercar
ハンドル捌きはシューマッハ
Steering skills like Schumacher
副操縦士はチューバッカ
Co-driver is Chewbacca
次元が違う連中ばっか (aye)
These guys are on a different level (aye)
コーナー攻めてるギリギリ
Attacking corners right on the edge
モーター全開地響き
Motors wide open, ground shaking
空から導き
Guidance from the sky
お肌がピチピチ
Skin feeling fresh and tight
タイヤ焦がしてドーナツターン
Tires smoking during a donut turn
弾き飛んでいくドラム缶
Drums flying away
顧客満足度が高くて
High customer satisfaction
ぶち上がってるお客様
Crowd going crazy wild
0から最高到達点
Going from zero to max peak
ためてる太陽光発電
Charging up on solar power
探索するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid
超覚醒突入ボーナスステージ (aye)
Super awakening, bonus stage (aye)
一直線伸びている道路
A straight road stretching out
vibrationエンジンの鼓動
Vibration of the engine's heartbeat
速度増し上がっている高度
Speed increasing, altitude rising
限界、重力、凌駕し上昇 (aye)
Shaking off limits and gravity, ascending (aye)
開拓しまくっていくフロンティア
Opening up the frontier
旅立つroadster only one
Setting out, roadster only one
アクセル踏み込んでいくドンピシャ
Stepping firmly on the accelerator
飛んでいく日本遺産
Japanese heritage flying by
1億馬力の重低音
A billion horsepower heavy bass
火星のホテルが休憩所
A hotel on Mars as our break room
並んで走行UFO
Racing side by side with UFOs
降り立つ宇宙ステーション
Landing at the space station
物語を継承 (aye) まるで
Continuing the story (aye) like
旧約聖書 (aye) この先
The testaments (aye) here on out
何世紀も成長 生き延びて
Growing for centuries, surviving
結果出すtake off
Making results, take off
叶えるはずだwon't stop
Dreams come true, we won't stop
心臓がモンスター
Our hearts are a monster
aliens turn it up
FG party hard
光るtesla roadster
Blingin' Tesla roadster
heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Awakening our instincts
青い炎 (woo! woo!)
Blue flames (woo! woo!)
BFF let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Prisoners to nothing, from naught to space
走るFG ROADSTER
Speeding the FG ROADSTER
鳴るbooster
Hitting that booster
FLOW GLOW the space to be
いまchase me
Now chase me
プロ民のみなさん楽しんでますか！？
Are you all enjoying yourselves, pro-min?!
FGちゃんたちももっともっとかます準備できてる！？
Are you FG girls ready to rock even harder?!
我々は翔ぶsuper girl
We're super girls flying high
金ピカの光 異次元
Golden light, another dimension
荒れ果てた世界パトロール
Patrolling a devastated world
解き放て 踊れ
Unleash, dance
私たち存在が純金
Our existence is pure gold
いつでも万端な準備
Always fully prepared
まるで無敵の宇宙人
Just like invincible aliens
春麗よりも俊敏
More agile than Chun-Li
サイドブレーキない突撃
Charging in without a handbrake
ハイボレテージ 毎回素敵
High voltage, always wonderful
催促です 愛をくれ
Reminding you, give me love
今 乗っかってる波の上 (ざっぷ〜ん)
Now riding on the waves (splosh~)
純度100%
100% purity
この爆発力 マクラーレン
This explosive power, McLaren
メッキに興味ない ルパン三世
Not interested in plating, Lupin the Third
この輝きなら ツタンカーメン
If it's this brilliance, Tutankhamun
髪 風受け なびかせ
Let your hair flutter in the wind
good, good, groove your body
let it rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock on
心を突き動かせ
Move your heart
good, good, groove your body
level up, up, up, up, up, up
look at me now
身に纏うflight suitは
The flight suit I'm wearing is
24K GOLD
ready to go
深い闇 照らす輝き
Brilliance illuminating deep darkness
24K GOLD
上に行こう
Let's go up
空 飛んでいるwassup
Flying in the sky, wassup
このケープが翼
This cape is wings
漲っているpower
Overwhelming power
戦っているsuper girl
Fighting super girls
全身駆け巡る 満タンのガソリン
Full tank of gasoline running through the body
黄金の流星だ パッと見
Golden meteor, at a glance
忍者みたい 半蔵 服部
Like a ninja, Hattori Hanzo
強くて 可愛くって かっこいい
Strong, cute, and cool
戦う 高鳴る
Fighting, heart beating fast
黄金の戦士 現る
Golden warrior appears
渋谷 新宿 原宿
Shibuya, Shinjuku, Harajuku
風となり ちはやぶる
Becoming the wind, Chihayaburu
絶対 撤退 命令ない
Absolutely no retreat order
アベンジャーズみたいな精鋭隊
Elite team like the Avengers
生成AIにはないオーラ
Aura that generative AI doesn't have
纏っている輝く生命体
A shining life form wrapped around us
髪 風受け なびかせ
Let your hair flutter in the wind
good, good, groove your body
let it rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock on
心を突き動かせ
Move your heart
good, good, groove your body
level up, up, up, up, up, up
look at me now
身に纏うflight suitは
The flight suit I'm wearing is
24K GOLD
ready to go
深い闇 照らす輝き
Brilliance illuminating deep darkness
解き放てlight up
Unleash, light up
金色の戦士FG fight up
Golden warrior, FG fight up
空 飛んでいるwassup
Flying in the sky, wassup
このケープが翼
This cape is wings
みなぎっているpower
Overwhelming power
戦っているsuper girl
Fighting super girls
全身駆け巡る 満タンのガソリン
Full tank of gasoline running through the body
黄金の流星だ パッと見
Golden meteor, at a glance
忍者みたい 半蔵 服部
Like a ninja, Hattori Hanzo
強くて 可愛くって かっこいい
Strong, cute, and cool
戦う 高鳴る
Fighting, heart beating fast
黄金の戦士 現る
Golden warrior appears
渋谷 新宿 原宿
Shibuya, Shinjuku, Harajuku
風となり ちはやぶる
Becoming the wind, Chihayaburu
絶対 撤退 命令ない
Absolutely no retreat order
アベンジャーズみたいな精鋭隊
Elite team like the Avengers
生成AIにはないオーラ
Aura that generative AI doesn't have
纏っている輝く生命体
A shining life form wrapped around us
髪 風受け なびかせ
Let your hair flutter in the wind
good, good, groove your body
let it rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock on
心を突き動かせ
Move your heart
good, good, groove your body
level up, up, up, up, up, up
look at me now
身に纏うflight suitは
The flight suit I'm wearing is
24K GOLD
ready to go
深い闇 照らす輝き
Brilliance illuminating deep darkness
24K GOLD
上に行こう
Let's go up
生成AIにはないオーラ
Aura that generative AI doesn't have
纏っている輝く生命体
A shining life form wrapped around us
我々は翔る super girl
We are soaring super girls,
金ピカの光 異次元
Golden light in other dimensions,
荒れ果てた世界 パトロール
Patrolling a desolate world,
解き放て 踊れ
Let loose and dance!
心を吹き動かせ
Stir your heart,
レディロココココココ...
Ready, rock, rock, rock...
身に纏う flight suit は
The flight suit we wear is
24k gold ready to go
深い闇照らす 輝き
Shining light piercing the deep darkness,
24k gold 上にゆこう
24K gold, let's go up!
この次のステージへ FG point
To the next stage, FG point!
FG! FG! FG! FG!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
フロログロー3Dライブをお披露目のご覧の皆さん！
Everyone watching the Flow Glow 3D live reveal!
What's up!
キレーイ！グローーーイ！フログラルデーーイ！
Beautiful! Glow-y! Flow Glow-day!
先程はFGロードスタート、
Earlier we delivered the FG Road Start,
テンニーフォーケイゴールドメドレー形式でお届けしました！ありがとうございます！
24K Gold medley format! Thank you!
いや、最初からド派手な登場すぎません ?
Man, wasn't that appearance way too flashy?
いやあれどうやったらみんなをわっ と驚かせられるかって考えて結果だよね ?
We thought about how to surprise everyone, right?
そうそう、どうせやるなら一番ド派手なほうで行こうって言って
Yeah, we wanted the absolute flashiest entrance!
モニターを突き破ってきました。
We punched right through the monitor!
いややりすぎだよ！
That's way too much!
まぁねそんな破ちゃめちゃすぎる私たちなんですけど、まずはね自己紹介の方からさせていただけたらなと思います。
Well, let's start with our self-introductions!
それでは私から！
Starting with me!
私の音に愛ででーアナインザハウス！
Falling in love with my sound, I'm in the house!
フロログローのリーダー、イサキリナです。ブラブラ！
Flow Glow's leader, Isaki Rina. Brrra!
次はニコ！ニコたんがきたー！
Next is Niko! Niko-tan has arrived!
フロライブデバイト、フログローのお笑い担当、コガネニコです。ニコたんだよ！
FlowLive part-timer Kogane Niko!
すーちゃん。
Suu-chan.
シエピシは数 の 充電足りてる ? フロライブデバイト、フログローのえらいせんせーと、水宮すうです！
Flow Glow's esteemed teacher, Mizumiya Suu!
次はチャハ！エンジン全開レッツゴー！
Next is Chacha! Engines full throttle!
フログローのDJ兼運転手担当、輪堂千速です！今日も盛り上がってこねー！
Flow Glow DJ and driver, Rindo Chacha!
次はビビ！
Next is Bibi!
はい、いきますよー！せーの、ビビー！
Yes, here we go! Ready, set... Bibi!
いつもキラキラなキキララビビです！わー！
Always sparkly, sparkling-bright Bibi!
みんな、今日もキラキラいこう！よろしく！よろしくお願いします！
Everyone, let's get even more hyped!
今日は私たち5人で最高のライブをお届けしていくぞ！行くぞー！
Today the five of us will deliver the best live!
さて、すでににお気づきかとは思うんですが、ついにフログローも3Dデビューしました！
Flow Glow has finally made its 3D debut!
ちなみにビビ、3Dになった自分の身体を見てどう思いますか ?
Bibi, what do you think of your 3D body?
いやーーこんなにキューティー、セクシー、ヘルシーでね、みんなもっとビビのこと好きになっちゃったな、ほんまに！
Being cutie, sexy, and healthy is the best!
なんやこのケツマジで！お尻やばすぎ！
What is this butt, seriously! So crazy!
交差事故になるから、パンツ見せるな！パンツでます！
It'll cause a traffic accident, don't show panties!
はい、ありがとね。チャハはどう ?
Yes, thanks. How about Chacha?
チャハはもっちろん、この太もも！ご覧ください、みんな！もっと見せて！もっと見せて！
Look at these thighs! Show more, show more!
ピンタイプだからね！だめだったかな。すーちゃんはどうですか ?
Because it's pin type! How about Suu-chan?
はい、スーはま、かっこいいかな ? みたいな。やっぱ行けてるかな ? みたいなね。
Suu is, well, cool? Wondering if I pull it off.
いやいやそんなキャラじゃなかったよ！水宮やって、かっこいい！
No, Mizumiya, you're totally cool!
ほら、見 てこんなにちっこいのにこんなに大きく見える！
Look, even though she's tiny, she looks big!
え、ニコたん？あ、そうだよ！ニコたん完全に虎！え？え？
Niko-tan is completely a tiger! Eh?
さっきまで2速歩行じゃなかった ?
Weren't you walking on two legs until now?
いや、ライブで踊るんだから、それ4速にはできないでしょ！
You can't do four legs at a live show!
見たことないよ、四足歩行のアイドルなんて！そんな飛ばして...
I've never seen a four-legged idol!
リアナはどうですか ? あ、そうですね。まああの...私も、あ、チョッパルセクシーなんですが...
How about Riliana? I'm also... choppy sexy...
キューティーセクシーなこのセクシーダンスをこの身体でお披露目できるかなと思うとすごく嬉しいです。素晴らしい！可愛いお話ですね。ありがとうございます！
I'm so happy to show off this cute/sexy dance!
そんな私たち5人ででお届けする3Dライブ、そのハッシュタグについてはニコ、説明よろしくお願いします！
Niko, please explain the hashtag for the live!
はーい！今日の3Dライブのハッシュタグ、右上をご覧ください！
Yes! Please look at the top right for the hashtag!
ハッシュタグ、FG3Dライブです！
The hashtag is FG3D Live!
スクショにこのハッシュタグを加えてXでたくさんポストしてください！お願いします！
Add it to your screenshots and post on X!
トレンド1位目指すぞらしいです！あと、
They say we're aiming for #1 on trending!
ライブを見てくれてるみんなね、ぜひコメントでこのFGちゃんたちに銭を贈ってください！よろしくお願いします！
Please send superchats to these FG girls!
はい、ニコ、ありがとう！
Yes, Niko, thank you!
はい、そしたらライブの中盤には、え、サプライズや重大発表もありますので、
Right, so in the second half of the live, we'll have surprises and major announcements,
ぜひ最後まで楽しんでいただけると嬉しいです。
so we hope you enjoy it all the way to the end!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
まさかしないでね？
Don't spoil it, okay?
でかさ、ちはやさん。
Hey, Chihaya-san.
はい、なんですか？
Yes, what is it?
福太郎を置いているのまずいかも。
Leaving Fukutaro there might be bad.
だめの？
Not allowed?
うん。
Yeah.
かっこいいよ。東京の路上駐車だめ。
It's cool. Street parking in Tokyo is not allowed.
東京の路上駐車だめ。
Street parking...
だめ？
Not allowed?
撤去されちゃうよ。
It'll get towed.
路上駐車だめ！
Street parking is not allowed!
来て来て！
Hurry, hurry!
やめて！やめて！
Stop it! Stop!
やめて、やめて！
Stop it, stop it!
だから、あの、繋いでおっから止めてきてもらって。
So, connect it and bring it back, okay?
触ってくれる？
Can you touch it?
うん、持ってから。
Yeah, because I'm holding it!
じゃ、次行こっか！
Alright, let's go!
次の曲だ！
Next song!
1曲目からFG Roadstarと
Starting with the first song, "FG Roadstar,"
24K GOLDをメドレー形式でお送りしてきました。
and "24K GOLD," we delivered them in a medley style!
なんと、そのFG Roadstarのサビの振り付けは
And guess what? The intro choreography for "FG Roadstar"
すーちゃんがしてくれたんだよね！
was actually created by Su-chan!
ちゃんとフード職を守れよ！
Protect the foundation!
かっこいいよね！
So cool, right?
みんなもね、ぜひいつか踊ってください。
We hope you all dance to it sometime too!
よろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to it!
ビビトラはメドレーやってみて、どうだった？
Bibitora, try doing a medley. How was it?
こうやってついにみんなに見てもらうことができて、めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！
So being able to finally show it to everyone now makes me so happy!
かっこよかったよー！
It was so cool, right?
かっこよかったよ！
It really was!
ニコはどうやった？
Nico, how was it for you?
そうだね！
That's true!
みんな深呼吸して！
Everyone, take a deep breath!
深呼吸！
Deep breath!
マインドフルネス開けてくれ！
Open up the mind-fullness!
その感想をね、あの、言いたかったんだけど、
We wanted to say those feelings,
うちら緊張してボロボロしてる。
we were so nervous we were falling apart.
やっぱりデビューしてから2曲出したね、
We released two original songs after our debut,
これからもね、フロクロのことをね、ずっとよろしくお願いします！
and we want to keep singing them forever!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
まだ2曲、2曲残ってっからね、こっからよ。
We still have two songs...
ありがとね、でボディさんありがと。あ、止めてきてくれたのもありがとう。
Thanks to the body, thanks! And thank you for stopping by!
ちょっとね、なんかファンの人の車が多すぎて、
There are just so many cars from fans,
全然ありやって。
totally parking everywhere.
とめちゃったから！
We just parked it anyway!
帰る気をつけて！
Be careful when you go home!
気をつけてね！
Be careful!
じゃあそろそろみんなもライブ見たいるかなって思うので、
Alright, since everyone's probably watching the live,
次の曲に参りたいと思います。
let's move on to the next song!
ついでにモニターも、なんか新しいものになりました！
And by the way, the monitors have become something new too!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
じゃあね、まだまだライブは続くので、
The live is still continuing,
ますます盛り上がっていきましょう！
so let's get even more excited and go!
それでは聞いてください、ロード。
Now then, please listen to this: LOAD.
世界中に配信するライブ ここはホロ
A live stream broadcasting across the world, here is holo.
80億の星のlights 照らす心
Lights of 8 billion stars illuminating our hearts.
通知がなる it's time to show my digital world
Notifications ring, it's time to show my digital world.
眠らせない朝まで カーソル合わせ 絵文字の上
Until a morning that won't let me sleep, cursor aligned above the emojis.
スタジオにいる 今日も 歌詞を書いている
I'm in the studio today too, writing lyrics.
ノートに変わる景色、相当 気づけばいたよ東京
Scenery turning into notes, before I knew it, I was in Tokyo.
夜空をみる 首都高 乗る 月に向かうボート
Looking at the night sky, Shuto Expressway, riding a boat heading for the moon.
みんなに見せる証拠 支えになれることを
Proof to show everyone, becoming a strength.
ネガなマインド捨て 見てるだけじゃ意味ない
Throw away negative mindsets, just watching has no meaning.
夢じゃなくなった夢 負けず嫌いで有名
A dream that stopped being a dream, unbeaten and unpopular.
どこにもない終点 君と見た星空の下
Nowhere to end up, under the starry sky we saw together.
届きそうな手 このデバイスがあれば
With a hand about to reach, if we have this device,
どこへでも行ける気がするよ 続く one way
feeling like we can go anywhere, continuing one way.
stay with me by my side 遠いとこへ
Stay with me by my side, far away,
2人でこの地球から virtual world
together from this globe, virtual world.
気にしない今何時 何万キロ離れても
Never mind the time, however many thousand kilometers apart,
my team flow glow すぐ行動開始
my team flow glow, starting action right away.
チャット止まない 24 調子がいい 今日
Chat doesn't stop 24, feeling good today.
カメラにする はいチーズ
Making it a camera, saying cheese.
乗っ取ってる 電波塔から放送する
Broadcasting from a transmission tower we've taken over.
世界に配信 みてみな このスタイル yeah
Broadcasting to the world, check it out, this style, yeah.
負ける気すらない 捨てていく無駄なpride
No intention of losing, throwing away useless pride.
できるよ このくらい みんなで今夜もparty all night
We can do this much, party all night tonight.
日々々に上がるprice やれるならu better try
Price going up day by day, if you can do it, you better try.
世界中に配信するライブ ここはホロ
A live stream broadcasting across the world, here is holo.
80億の星のlights 照らす心
Lights of 8 billion stars illuminating our hearts.
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
Wearing pajamas, joining the morning meeting
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My brain is empty, that's my routine
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
From start to finish, mute screen
朝起きて えらい
Morning comes, good for you
傘持っててて えらい
Bringing an umbrella, good for you
ネガティブ あり得ない
Negative thoughts, no way
自由に気分をリライト
Freely rewriting my mood
背伸びしない 遠慮しない
Not stretching myself, not holding back
やばいくらいゆるい my vibe
It's loose to the point of being crazy, that's my vibe
描いていくカラーは自分次第
The colors I draw are up to me
オチない話を続ける鬼才
A genius who keeps telling stories without a punchline
行き先決めないっていうフリースタイル
Freestyle, never deciding on a destination
指さされたけど、気分はフライ
I was pointed at, but my mood is flying
眠たい、眠たい、眠らない tonight
Sleepy, sleepy, but not sleeping tonight
踊れレッドパーティガール
Dance, red party girl!
態度デカイのは長所にかけて
Having a big attitude is a strength,
いいってお母さんが言ってた。
Mom said it's okay.
フィルター越しの snap でピース
Peace sign in a snap through a filter
本当の事は虹の彼方に
The truth is beyond the rainbow
リアルもフェイクも just like a piece
Real or fake, it's just like a piece
so who decides what’s real?
not cool but good good enough
i'm still good good good enough
ちょっと loose but good good enough
A little loose but good good enough
i'm still good good good enough
もっと fuel but good good enough
More fuel but good good enough
i'm still good good good enough
not good but good good enough
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
Wearing pajamas, joining the morning meeting
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My brain is empty, that's my routine
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
From start to finish, mute screen
朝起きて えらい
Morning comes, good for you
傘持っててて えらい
Bringing an umbrella, good for you
ネガティブ あり得ない
Negative thoughts, no way
自由に気分をリライト
Freely rewriting my mood
背伸びしない 遠慮しない
Not stretching myself, not holding back
やばいくらいゆるい my vibe
It's loose to the point of being crazy, that's my vibe
描いていくカラーは自分次第
The colors I draw are up to me
オチない話を続ける鬼才
A genius who keeps telling stories without a punchline
行き先決めないっていうフリースタイル
Freestyle, never deciding on a destination
指さされたけど、気分はフライ
I was pointed at, but my mood is flying
眠たい、眠たい、眠らない tonight
Sleepy, sleepy, but not sleeping tonight
態度デカイのは長所にかけて
Having a big attitude is a strength,
いいってお母さんが言ってた。
Mom said it's okay.
フィルター越しの snap でピース
Peace sign in a snap through a filter
本当の事は虹の彼方に
The truth is beyond the rainbow
リアルもフェイクも just like a piece
Real or fake, it's just like a piece
so who decides what’s real?
誤字脱字、日常茶飯事
Typos and omissions, daily routine
また見過し、寝過し
Missing things again, oversleeping
それも生きてる証
That too is proof of living
未完成だからこそつくプレ値
Because it's unfinished, it gets a premium price
磨けば必ず光る前提
Assuming it will definitely shine if polished
誤字脱字、日常茶飯事
Typos and omissions, daily routine
また見過し、寝過し
Missing things again, oversleeping
それも生きてる証
That too is proof of living
未完成だからこそつくプレ値
Because it's unfinished, it gets a premium price
夢見てたときの自分はチャイルド
I was a child when I was dreaming
今日まで集めたフル装備でファイト
Fighting with the full equipment I've collected until today
ビビりだからこそ高めるマインド
Because I'm a coward, I raise my mind
褒めたい、褒めたい、たまに褒められたい
Want to be praised, want to be praised, sometimes want to be praised
（言葉じゃ足りない）
(Words aren't enough)
愛想がいいのは赤ちゃんのかたからって
Grandma also said I've been friendly since I was a baby.
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
Wearing pajamas, joining the morning meeting
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My brain is empty, that's my routine
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
From start to finish, mute screen
誤字脱字、日常茶飯事
Typos and omissions, daily routine
また見過し、寝過し
Missing things again, oversleeping
それも生きてる証
That too is proof of living
未完成だからこそつくプレ値
Because it's unfinished, it gets a premium price
磨けば必ず光る前提
Assuming it will definitely shine if polished
フィルター越しの snap でピース
Peace sign in a snap through a filter
本当の事は虹の彼方に
The truth is beyond the rainbow
リアルもフェイクも just like a piece
Real or fake, it's just like a piece
so who decides what’s real?
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
Wearing pajamas, joining the morning meeting
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My brain is empty, that's my routine
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
From start to finish, mute screen
Once upon a time
there was a little girl
君に良く似た
Looking so much like you,
oh darling
君に似てた
she looked just like you.
彼女はまるでタイガーアイ
She was just like a tiger's eye.
無数の欲より大事な夢を見つけては捕まえてしまった
Finding a dream more precious than endless desires, she caught it.
ある夜雨が降ってた
One night, it was raining.
濡れた瞳にぼやけた
Blurred in her dewy eyes,
嘘のように美しい
as beautiful as a lie,
ダリアが微笑んでた
a dahlia was smiling.
i want the same one
それが欲しいと言って吐き捨てた
she spat out, saying that's what she wanted.
引き換えに何が欲しい？
What do you want in return?
奏でろ賛美歌 無知なメロディーはハイ
Play a hymn, an ignorant melody is high—
たかが心なら差し上げたいわ
If it's just my heart, I'd gladly give it away.
and then i… 甘ったるい願いね
And then I... what a sickly sweet wish.
そして彼女は just a ダリアのように
And then she... just like a dahlia—
no… ダリア
no... a dahlia.
あの少女は
That girl
美しくない
wasn't beautiful,
歌声だけよ
she only had her voice,
まるで罪人
like a sinner.
思い返すと歌声すら誰も聞いてくれなかった
Looking back, no one even listened to her voice.
ah i don't give a shit, oh she don't give a shit
ああ誰が悪いのか？え きみ？きみ？きみ？
Ah, who's to blame? Eh, you? You? You?
oh ハニー大事でしょ 生きてく為に
Oh, honey, it's important to survive.
選ばれるより選ぶ人生
A life where you choose rather than be chosen.
君の才能なんできっとダリアのせいで
Your talent was probably trampled down by dahlia,
踏み潰されて彼女みたいに全部捨てたくなるわ
making you want to throw it all away like her.
ya これでわかったでしょう
Yeah, you get it now, right?
mm それでも必要？
Mm, is it still necessary?
ah 煙たがられたいの 私は違う 私は違う
Ah, do you want to be shunned? I'm different, I'm different.
改めまして一条莉央奈です 名前覚えて帰ってください
Once again, I'm Riona Ichijo! Please remember my name before you leave!
乱心 内心 邁進 ego
Distracted mind, inner mind, pressing forward, ego,
up & down いつも get into trouble
up & down, always get into trouble.
「楽しい」「正しい」「嬉しい」でも
"Fun", "right", "happy", but
平常 me、sold out
normal me is sold out.
あれナシ これナシ
No that, no this,
合わせる段々敵なし
adapting step by step, with no rivals.
己の way？
My own way?
違える (no, no)
Getting it wrong (no, no),
またゼロへ get away
back to zero, get away.
wisper to my ears oh give me some more details
Whisper to my ears, oh give me some more details.
手招き 脱して 勝し
Beckoning, breaking free, winning—
no way slipping and breaking down
かませ 急上昇
Fire away, soaring up fast,
はなて 絶好調 own way now
unleash your peak condition, own way now!
better show what i gotta gotta show！
Better show what I gotta gotta show!
ima shake it, lets go. next！
Ima shake it, let's go, next!
変ブ 理想像
Metamorphic ideal image,
come again, 熱狂
come again, frenzy!
hey show me what you got
i'm breaking down pretty me
next side next side…
next side, next side...
楽しんだれ up boomboom！
Enjoy it all, up boomboom!
trip in the dark…
Trip in the dark...
such a funny thing for me to explain
it's ok even if you don't understand
l just wanna make you roll
I just wanna make you roll,
ルールはない unchain
with no rules, unchain!
頭と心 awake now
Head and heart awake now,
アブラカダブラ blah blah blah 幻なら
abracadabra blah blah blah, if it's an illusion,
無理×3 価値なし 無視 ah just do it！
impossible x3, worthless, ignore it, ah just do it!
are you ready let's play game！！
Are you ready, let's play game!!
万人 万事 愛しては 一蓮托生 三千世界
Loving everyone and everything, sharing the same fate across three thousand worlds.
dancing 突進 童心 get up
Dancing, charging forward, childlike heart, get up,
全方位 call out
call out in all directions.
人生も 来世も
In this life and the next life,
i wish days were longer than 24
曇りなくいたいの yeah
I want to be free of clouds, yeah,
i'm feeling really mellow
oh i wanna feel more
たまには わがままに
sometimes being selfish—
now hey, come in and turn it loud
鳴らせ 鼓動を
Ring out the heartbeat,
醒ませ 最高潮 own way now
wake up to the peak, own way now!
better show what i gotta gotta show…
Better show what I gotta gotta show...
gotta show what i wanna wanna show！
Gotta show what I wanna wanna show!
ima shake it, lets go. next！
Ima shake it, let's go, next!
変幻 理想像
Shapeshifting ideal image,
come again, 熱狂
come again, frenzy!
hey show me what you got
i'm breaking down pretty me
next side next side…
next side, next side...
楽しんだれ up boomboom！
Enjoy it all, up boomboom!
na na na yeah
na na na na na na na na
let's make it loud！
let's make it loud!
la-ta-ta-tat！
La-ta-ta-tat!
next side next side…
Next side, next side...
楽しんだれ up boomboom！
Enjoy it all, up boomboom!
一度はあの光を見たんだよ とってもキレイで
Once, I saw that light, so very beautiful,
でも今思えば汚かった あれはいわゆるBad Day Dreams
but looking back now, it was so filthy. Those were so-called Bad Day Dreams.
光が眩しすぎて周りが見えず ただただ日々を
The light was too blinding to see around me, just spending my days
棒に振っていたあの日は 今だから笑えるよ
in vain. Those days I wasted, I can laugh about now.
一度はあの幕を開けたんだよ とっても重くて
Once, I opened that curtain, it was so heavy,
プレッシャー、イヤ味それに勝つためだけに ただ嫌なヤツで
just to win against the pressure and snide remarks, being just a nasty person.
そして気が付くと真っ暗な部屋に 一人ぼっちだった
And before I knew it, in a pitch-dark room, I was all alone.
終わった…もう戻れない…なんて…歩くのもやめた…
It's over... I can't go back... or so I thought... I even stopped walking...
でもI'm not alone. I'm not alone. We're not, We're not, We're not alone
But I'm not alone, I'm not alone. We're not, We're not, We're not alone.
お金じゃ買えないもの手に入れて
Getting something money can't buy,
もう一度光浴びて
bathing in the light once more.
そして今度は騙されないように
And this time so I won't be fooled,
僕らは今目指すよ 欲望に満ちた青年団
we are now aiming for it, the youth group filled with desire.
誰かが言った言葉 それすらその時は流して
The words someone said, I just let them pass by at the time,
今になって気付いたよ 欲望に負けた少年団
and now I've realized, the boy band that lost to desire.
So I know you know? You know I know? We've had, We've had, We've had glow?
狂われないように上向いて歩く
Walking looking up so I won't go mad.
もう一度光浴びて
Bathing in the light once more,
そして今度は騙されないように 僕らは今目指すよ
and this time so I won't be fooled, we are now aiming for it,
欲望に満ちた青年団 誰かが言った言葉 それすらその時は流して
the youth group filled with desire. The words someone said, I just let them pass by at the time,
今になって気付いたよ 欲望に負けた少年団
and now I've realized, the boy band that lost to desire.
んー、おはよ 朝起きてまず確認 きょうもいい感じだね
Hmm, good morning, waking up to check first: looks like a great day today.
1年365日 私のこと一番みてるひと 好きですと、言えるのは
365 days a year, the person who looks at me the most—saying "I love you"
当たり前とかじゃない 1日86400秒 ずっと付き合ってくんだから
isn't something to take for granted. 86,400 seconds a day, since we'll be together forever.
ママから聞いたことあるわ 似た人を好きになるんじゃなくて 好きの人には似るものらしいです
I've heard from my mom: it's not that you fall in love with someone similar, it seems you come to resemble the person you love.
本当です みんな思ったことあるわ 目を開けたら違う自分になって
That's true! Everyone has thought about it: opening your eyes to find yourself changed—
いやいやもっと真剣に変身します ますがつのりおやふふふ
no, no, transforming even more seriously! Masu katsunori oyafufufu
マスクの日は フルフルフル？
Is mask day full of fluff?
あれ 可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも さすがに盛りすぎちゃったかも
Wait, did I get too cute? Maybe I went overboard!
あなたの真似っ子なんですだって 超大好きなんだから
I'm just copying you because I love you so much!
鏡よ鏡もちょっとだけ 可愛くなってもいいのかな
Mirror, mirror, is it okay if I get a little cuter too?
いつだって 正直に言って
Always tell me honestly,
それで 秘密 秘密 秘密の可愛い子ちゃんにはなれない
and yet I can't become your secret cute girl.
そんなことぜんぶお見通しです
I see right through all of that,
だって逆に 秘密 秘密 秘密は私初心者にはいらない
because a beginner like me doesn't need secrets.
だけどあなたが秘密にするほど 可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも
Yet the more you keep secrets, the cuter I became.
朝起きて そうだ休み やりたいことありすぎ
Wake up in the morning, day off, too much to do.
一日は24時間って言うけどずっと起きてるわけでもない
They say a day is 24 hours, but I'm not awake the whole time.
帰ったら また確認 当たり前とかじゃない とにかく自分を大事にしましょう
Let's cherish ourselves above all.
ずっと付き合っていくんだから ママから聞いたことあるわ
Since we're together forever, I heard this from my mama:
10時から2時は寝るのがよくて 6時以降は食べないほうがいいけどいや無理です
Sleeping from 10 to 2 is best, and no eating after 6... yeah, no way!
みんな思ったことあるわ 寝てる間に変わらないのかな いやいややって
Everyone's thought about it: do we change while sleeping?
実際に神経に変身した
Actually transformed into nerves.
マスクの日は フルフルフル？ あれ可愛くなりすぎちゃったっていい
Is mask day full of fluff? It's fine if I got too cute.
本当に盛りすぎちゃっていい あなたのこと好きです
It's fine if I went overboard, I love you.
だって 超前向きなんだから 鏡よ鏡もちょっとだけ
Because I'm super positive! Mirror, mirror, just a little bit
可愛くなってもいいのかな いつだって 正直に言って
is it okay if I get cuter? Always tell me honestly.
もー大好きです 大好きです 目の前の君に言っていいのかな
I love you so much, can I say that to you right in front of me?
自分にいま魔法かけます 嘘でもかかったふりしてね
I'm casting a spell on myself now, pretend it worked even if it's a lie.
でも私もうあなたも嘘がつけない そういうやつだからさ
Neither you nor I can tell lies anymore, that's just the kind of people we are.
マスクの日は フルフルフル？ あれ可愛くなりすぎちゃったっていい
Is mask day full of fluff? It's fine if I got too cute.
本当に盛りすぎちゃっていい あなたのこと好きです
It's fine if I went overboard, I love you.
だって 超前向きなんだから 鏡よ鏡もちょっとだけ
Because I'm super positive! Mirror, mirror, just a little bit
可愛くなってもいいのかな いつだって 正直に言って
is it okay if I get cuter? Always tell me honestly.
あれ可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも さすがに盛りすぎちゃったかも
Wait, did I get too cute? Maybe I went a bit overboard!
あなたの真似っ子なんですだって 超大好きなんだから
I'm just copying you because I love you so much!
鏡よ鏡もちょっとだけ 可愛くなってもいいのかな
Mirror, mirror, is it okay if I get a little cuter too?
いつだって 正直に言って
Always tell me honestly,
それで 秘密 秘密 秘密の可愛い子ちゃんにはなれない
and yet I can't become your secret cute girl.
そんなことぜんぶお見通しです
I see right through all of that,
だって逆に 秘密 秘密 秘密は私初心者にはいらない
because a beginner like me doesn't need secrets.
だけどあなたが秘密にするほど 可愛くなりすぎちゃった
Yet the more you keep secrets, the cuter I became.
終わらない夜の途中
In the middle of the endless night,
灯を忘れた空には
in the sky that forgot its lights,
戻れない日の指切りを カシオペヤの代わりに
I traded promises of days we can't return to for Cassiopeia.
鳥になった宝物が 落とす影を追っていたら
While chasing the shadows dropped by treasures turned into birds,
真っ暗にまぎれて混ざり 見つけられないままで
I got lost in pitch darkness, unable to find them.
いくつめのドアを開けて 繰り返し景色を泳ぐ
Opening how many doors, swimming through repeating scenery,
心がまだ疲えながら そのためだけに動いている
though my heart is still exhausted, it beats just for that.
これはきっと帰り道 夢の向こうに続く道
This is surely the way back, leading beyond our dreams.
擦り切れた歌を纏えば 何も怖くはない
Clad in a worn-out song, there is nothing to fear.
命は理由に出会えた 燃えて消える意味を知った
Life found its reason, knowing the meaning of burning away.
その火が視界を照らした 青く青くどこまでも
That fire illuminated my vision, blue and ever so blue anywhere.
明日がすべてを失っても あなたの鼓動だけは歌ってほしい
Even if tomorrow loses everything, I want only your heartbeat to keep singing.
あなたのことだけは歌ってほしい
I want you to sing only about me,
ならば私は戦える
then I can fight.
たとえこの耳鳴り消えないとしても
Even if this ringing in my ears won't fade away,
思い出せなくなった虹を覚えてる空には
In a sky that remembers the rainbow I couldn't recall,
度々裸足が響くよ
bare feet echo repeatedly.
それでも歩いていると
Even so, as I keep walking,
掴もうとしてすり抜けた
whatever I tried to grasp slipped through my fingers.
ことを忘れない手のひら
My palm doesn't forget that feeling.
指を二つにして隠して
Crossing two fingers to hide it,
強さに変える魔法を
the magic that turns it into strength—
あとどれだけ息をしたら
how much longer do I have to breathe
これでよかったと思える？
to feel like this was for the best?
心がずっとくたびれながら
While my heart keeps getting weary,
欠片の全部で動いている
everything in these fragments is moving.
これはきっと帰り道 あの人と同じじゃなくていい
This is surely my way back, it doesn't have to be the same as that person's.
ただもう一度だけ会いたい 何も怖くない
I just want to meet you one more time, I'm not afraid of anything anymore.
泣かないでって祈るのは 足元の下の涙
Praying "don't cry" are the tears beneath my feet.
迷いをのっけたつま先で 進め 進め魂ごと
With tiptoes carrying hesitation, push forward, push forward with all my soul!
正しいかどうかなんてことよりも あなたのいる世界が笑ってほしい
More than whether it's right or wrong, I want the world where you are to smile.
だから私は生きている 時計の針にも奪えない力で
That's why I'm alive, with a power that even the hands of a clock cannot steal.
鳥に奪われた宝物が落とす影 まだ探してる
I'm still searching for the shadow cast by the treasure stolen by birds.
ああ もう一度だけ会いたい 何も怖くない
Ah, I just want to meet you one more time, I'm not afraid of anything.
命は理由に出会えた 燃えて消える意味を知った
Life found a reason, and learned the meaning of burning up and fading away.
その日が世界を照らした 青く青くどこまでも
That day illuminated the world, endlessly blue and deep.
明日がすべてを失っても
Even if tomorrow loses everything,
繋げたことだけは歌ってほしい
I want you to sing at least that we connected.
だから私は生きている
That's why I'm alive.
欠片の全部で祈るんだよ 足元の下の涙
I pray with all my fragments, the tears beneath my feet.
迷いをのっけたつま先で 進め 進め魂ごと
With tiptoes carrying hesitation, push forward, push forward with all my soul!
間違いかどうかなんてことよりも あなたのいる世界が続いてほしい
More than whether it's a mistake, I want the world where you are to keep going.
ならば私は戦える たとえその時傍にいないとしても
Then I can fight, even if I'm not by your side at that time.
この地球 全てがウェナソビュ
This earth, everything is wena-so-byu,
半端なカッコで出すのよ本気
putting out serious vibes with half-baked style.
リアルに一人きりのヴィヴィッド 剥き出しの命
Really, a solitary vivid, raw life.
なんでそんなに自信があるんですか？
Why are you so confident?
爪で掴んだ結果は当たり前じゃん
The results grasped with nails are obvious, right?
リアルに一人きりの皮肉よ 放つきみの名前
Truly a solitary irony, releasing your name.
音を食え 栄養を食え 爪の垢煎じて飲もうぜ
Eat the sound, eat the nutrients, brew and drink the dirt from my nails!
手持ち味無い味を味を活かせ
Make the most of whatever flavor you hold.
迷え もう一回 思いがいてどうしたいってだってさ 浮き世換わりは華々しく
Get lost once more, wondering what you want to do—after all, changing the floating world is magnificent!
夢を越えろ そこから上を向けよ
Transcend your dreams, look up from there!
リアルに上を上をげよう げよう ここまで来いよ 噛み砕け 噛み砕け
Really raise it up, up—come this far, chew it up, chew it up!
噛み砕け 噛み砕け
Chew it up, chew it up!
この地球上全てが俺の遊び場
This entire world is my playground,
半端な覚悟で汚すなよ坊や
don't mess around half-heartedly, kid.
リアリスト気取りのビビり屋 話になんねえ
You act tough as a realist, but you're a coward—your talk is meaningless.
「なんでそんなに自信があるんですか？」
"Why are you so confident?"
手前で掴んだ結果だ当たり前じゃん
It's obvious from the results I've achieved.
ジャーナリスト気取りの皮肉屋 話す気になんねえ
You act like a journalist, but you're just sarcastic—no intention of talking.
毒を喰らえ栄養を喰らえ
Swallow the poison, consume the nutrients,
テメェの味出しで決まる持ち味を活かせ
bring out the flavor determined by your unique taste.
one way or another way お前が一体どうしたいかってだ
One way or another way, it's about what you truly want,
さあおかわりはいかがですか？
so would you like seconds?
夢を越えろ
Transcend the dreams,
そこから上を向けよ
look up from there.
本物に飢えろ
Hunger for authenticity,
ここまで来いよ
come this far.
come at me…
Come at me...
夢を越えろ そこから上を向けよ
Transcend the dreams, look up from there,
リアルに飢えろ
hunger for reality.
ここまで来いよ
Come this far.
カンマ止め カンマ止め
Comma, stop... comma, stop...
夢を越えろ そこから上を向けよ
Transcend the dreams, look up from there,
リアルに飢えろ ここまで来いよ
hunger for reality, come this far.
カンマ止め カンマ止め
Comma, stop... comma, stop...
待てない 待たない
Can't wait, won't wait,
いくらあっても足りない
no matter how much I have, it's not enough.
腹いっぱい 食べたい
I want to eat my fill,
手間をヤットコサラライ
and breeze through the hassle.
顎の骨砕く 獲取るのが勝負
Crushing jaws, taking the prize is everything.
アリシモトモクモ クラスモーク 上級のフルコース
From top to bottom, a high-class full course.
縦軸横軸は通ず
Vertical and horizontal axes align,
ウォッチングコツ上手 もっとシャープシャープボトノース
watching skillfully, even sharper at the bottom.
ストップの時でコートだ 頂上のタッパー
At the stop, it's the coat, the top-tier topper.
夢を越えろ
Transcend the dreams,
そこから上を向けよ
look up from there.
リアルに飢えろ
Hunger for reality,
ここまで来いよ
come this far.
come at me…
Come at me...
カンマ止め カンマ止め
Comma, stop... comma, stop...
夢を越えろ そこから上を向けよ
Transcend the dreams, look up from there,
リアルに飢えろ ここまで来いよ
hunger for reality, come this far.
カンマ止め カンマ止め
Comma, stop... comma, stop...
夢を越えろ そこから上を向けよ
Transcend the dreams, look up from there,
リアルに飢えろ ここまで来いよ
hunger for reality, come this far.
あれが正解なんて 誰の成れの果て？
Heh, you say those answers are what fits—who's there to tell me I'm not it?
答えも欲しいのも一個でこれだけ 悩んだってしょうがないじゃない
Gimme likes, replies, but one? That's all? Numbers fall, no use worrying.
あれは夢だったと思うことにしたって (つらw)
I tried thinking it was all a dream (too bad)...
でも全然思えないんだけど
but I just can't see it that way.
助けてフォロワー！ 抗うだけ
Help me, save me, followers! Just fighting back,
若さに負け
losing to youth,
next, next lucky lucky & lucky!
オーリーオー 割り切れたらさ オーリーオー 楽なのとか
Oh eh oh, why can't I just let it go? Oh eh oh, maybe take it slow.
もうヤダ！ なんていう新世界か！
Ah, I've had enough! What kind of new world is this?!
あなた以外は あなた以外はいらない
It's you I want, nobody else.
はらないでよバリア あるはずなのは何か
Don't put up barriers, what's meant to be is out there.
あったんならば happy! jumpin' yeah!
And if we found it, happy! jumpin' yeah!
あなたのその手とあたしのこの手を つないだらもう二度と離さないわ
Hand in hand, you and me, we'll never be apart again.
あなたのその手があたしのこの手を 掴んだら…以後お見知り置きを！my love♡
Cuz babe, once you touch my hand, there's no escape—my love♡
あれが正解なんて 誰の成れの果て？
Heh, you say those answers are what fits—who's there to tell me I'm not it?
答えも欲しいのも一個でこれだけ 悩んだってしょうがないじゃない
Gimme likes, replies, but one? That's all? Numbers fall, no use worrying.
あれは夢だったと思うことにしたって
I tried thinking it was all a dream,
でも全然思えないんだけど 助けてフォロワー！
but I just can't see it that way—help me, followers!
抗うだけ 若さに負け
Just fighting back, losing to youth,
next, next lucky lucky & lucky!
オーリーオー 割り切れたらさ オーリーオー 楽なのとか
Oh eh oh, why can't I just let it go? Oh eh oh, maybe take it slow.
もうヤダ！ なんていう新世界か！
Ah, I've had enough! What kind of new world is this?!
あなた以外は あなた以外はいらない
It's you I want, nobody else.
はらないでよバリア あるはずなのは何か
Don't put up barriers, what's meant to be is out there.
あったんならば happy! jumpin' yeah!
And if we found it, happy! jumpin' yeah!
あなたのその手とあたしのこの手を つないだらもう二度と離さないわ
Hand in hand, you and me, we'll never be apart again.
目と目が合えば i know キミこそが相棒
When our eyes meet I know, you are the only partner.
メロつかせる才能 (What?)
The talent to make me melt (what?)
エンジン全開 let's go
Engines full throttle, let's go!
盛り上がってい行くぞ let's go
Let's get hyped and go!
ログオンの準備足りてる 足りてないやな
Is your login ready? Not quite yet?
後半戦も盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let's heat up for the second half!
みんなのハートもっとメロメロにしちゃうぞ
We're gonna make everyone's hearts melt even more!
後半戦もまっせな！ うー ビビッ！
Get ready for the second half! Ooh, vivid!
みんなに出会えてとっても幸せです 画面の向こうのみんな声出せ ボラーー！
We're so happy to meet you all—everyone on the other side of the screen, make some noise!
新しい姿のフロクロで新しい曲聴いてくれ make it break it!
Listen to our new song in our new FLOW GLOW style—make it, break it!
make it break it! make it break it!
目と目が合えば i know キミこそが相棒
When our eyes meet I know, you are the only partner.
メロつかせる才能 make it break it!
The talent to make me melt—make it, break it!
パパッと見天使でも 中には潜むデーモン
Even if you look like an angel at first glance, there's a demon inside.
soギャップと愛嬌あれば最強 haterはシカト
So with charm and a gap, you're strongest—ignore the haters.
一連托生オーガナイズ 退屈に用はない
In it together, organize—I have no use for boredom.
一線引くよボーダーライン 届かない？しょうがない
I'll draw a border line—can't reach? It can't be helped.
ウチらが集まればバッド baddest 見惚れちゃうでしょ？
If we gather, we're the baddest—you'll be enchanted, won't you?
look at me, look at me now...
照らし出すでしょって 紙一重
Illuminating us, it's a razor-thin margin.
置いてかないで the time, ついて来て vibe MCs
Don't leave us behind the time, come along vibe MCs.
本気の Friday night, Make it, Break it
Serious Friday night, Make it, Break it.
メガレボリューション、明日を貫け、
Mega Revolution, pierce through tomorrow,
かぶけ、夢に恋、恋、恋の...
show off, falling in love with dreams...
Prayer is never stop, 真ん中ぶち抜け、
Prayer is never stop, blast right through the center,
揺げ、限界より鼓動!
shake it, beat beyond your limits!
Make it, break it, Make it, break it
Make it, break it
Bang, bang, bang, you see!
Make it, break it, Make it, break it
ほらどっちにするの？
Hey, which one will you choose?
どんどん加速する鼓動、If you wanna be my man,
Heartbeats accelerating, If you wanna be my man,
嘘見とかはなしで...
no playing hard to get...
ほに、もっと、ほら、もっと、あずわっさっぺ
Honi, more, look, more, what's up then
ばに、ほっ、と、もっと、ほっ、と、はにー、なっさっぺ
Honey, hot, and, more, hot, and, honey, what's up then
置いてかないで the time,
Don't leave us behind the time,
ついて来て vibe MCs, 本気の Friday night,
come along vibe MCs, serious Friday night,
Make it, Break it
Brand new generation, 感じるままから、
Brand new generation, from how we feel,
赤裸々、絡みこに、おりおりお、ワンサイズ、
bare, intertwining, folding and folding, one size,
連ねるバラ、そこ抜け出せ、
lining up roses, break right out of there,
ざこて、手上げて、愛て、ネリわな
Slip right through and set the trap—
You see, Make it, Break it
Make it, Break it
Bang, bang, bang!
You see, Make it, Break it
Make it, Break it
頭までメガナイト! FG行くぞ!
Mega night straight to our heads! FG, let's go!
メガレボリューション、明日を貫け、
Mega Revolution, pierce through tomorrow,
かぶけ、夢に恋、恋、恋の...
show off, falling in love with dreams...
Prayer is never stop, 真ん中ぶち抜け、
Prayer is never stop, blast right through the center,
揺げ、限界より鼓動!
shake it, beat beyond your limits!
ずっと色褪せない みんなとの first day
The first day with everyone that never fades,
いつもより濃いメイク あれはフェイクフェイス
heavier makeup than usual, that's a fake face.
無理して作ったハリボテ 期待と不安詰め込んで
A papier-mâché made by forcing it, packing hopes and anxieties,
歩き出したんだ、せーので 強がってた
we started walking, on the count of three—acting tough.
I was like a villain でも皆に気づかされた そのままでえやん
I was like a villain, but everyone made me realize it's fine just as I am.
語り合ったりじゃないこの日々 バチャになっても一緒にいたい by vivi
These days aren't just about talking, we want to stay together even as avatars, by Vivi.
気づいたら騒がしい 毎日違う歩幅
Before we knew it, it's noisy with different strides every day,
どこに行くの私たち 迷う自分
where are we heading, losing ourselves?
皆くれる刺激 まれ愛じゃない これって素敵?
The stimulation everyone gives, isn't it rare love? Isn't this wonderful?
まだ leader って胸張れなくても 持ってる何かがあるよ
Even if we can't proudly call ourselves leaders yet, we have something.
縦になる覚悟 チームのため私歌って踊るステージ
Ready to stand tall, singing and dancing for the team on stage,
プログロウ 刻むビート めくる next page
FLOW GLOW carving the beat, turning the next page.
stay by my side 夜中になっても まだ寝れない yeah
stay by my side, even in the middle of the night, still can't sleep, yeah
あとどれくらいでたどり着く あの夢の世界
how much longer until we reach that dream world?
初めて会ったあの日 また輪になって遊んだり ここまで歩いてきた
The day we first met, playing in a circle again, we've walked all this way.
me and you 今でも覚えてる
Me and you, I still remember.
stay by my side 街角で二人 by my side
stay by my side, two people at the street corner, by my side
考えてる一人 無駄にはならないから
thinking alone, because it won't be in vain,
あの涙も今ここ by my side 寄り添ってる隣
those tears are now right here, by my side, snuggling close beside me.
ずっと昔はぐれた炎 夜を必死に照らしたこと
The flame that strayed long ago, desperately illuminating the night,
集まる星は踊る鼓動 それは波長 これからも残る音 暗闇の中見えない R.A.Y
gathering stars, dancing heartbeat, that's our resonance, a sound that will remain—invisible R.A.Y in the darkness.
道しるべはあなたのサイン (繋いで) 光よこの手を離さないで
Our guidepost is your sign (connecting), light, don't let go of this hand.
宇宙の始まりより煌めいて さえ、いいストーリー 同じ夢追い i じゃない we もう一人じゃない
Sparkling brighter than the universe's beginning, a good story, chasing the same dream, not just 'I', we're no longer alone.
々やばい FLOW GLOW の宇宙 可能性は未知数 とりま配信に夢中
Wild FLOW GLOW universe, possibilities are unknown, obsessed with streaming for now.
いつか皆で行こうワイキキ la la land c'est la vie vip 楽しみたい日々
Let's all go to Waikiki someday, la la land, c'est la vie, VIP days we want to enjoy.
どこが name りに込めた 4 人をあたしたちはやれるきっと from rindo
Putting into our name, the four of us can definitely do it, from Rindo.
stay by my side 夜中になっても まだ寝れない yeah
stay by my side, even in the middle of the night, still can't sleep, yeah
あとどれくらいでたどり着く あの夢の世界
how much longer until we reach that dream world?
初めて会ったあの日 また輪になって遊んだり ここまで歩いてきた
The day we first met, playing in a circle again, we've walked all this way.
me and you 今でも覚えてる
Me and you, I still remember.
上がるペース 夜も寝れず置き去りにした生活リズム
Pacing up, leaving behind the sleep-deprived daily rhythm,
たたまには一度振り返る 別にまったりしたっていいんじゃない?
sometimes looking back once, wouldn't it be fine to just relax?
比較 自己嫌悪 途方もない 一人で抱え込むなよ ほら水くさい
Comparison, self-loathing, overwhelming, don't shoulder it all alone, don't be so distant.
5人 自分らしくいりゃ心配ない 美味しいもの食べに行こう 月1
As long as the five of us are ourselves, no worries, let's go eat something delicious once a month.
stay by my side 夜中になっても まだ寝れない yeah
stay by my side, even in the middle of the night, still can't sleep, yeah
あとどれくらいでたどり着く あの夢の世界
how much longer until we reach that dream world?
初めて会ったあの日 また輪になって遊んだり ここまで歩いてきた みえゆ 今でも覚えてる
The day we first met, playing in a circle again, we've walked all this way, me and you, I still remember.
まだ覚えてる
I still remember
stay by my side 街角で二人
stay by my side, the two of us on the street corner
by my side 考えてるひとり
by my side, thinking all alone
無駄にはならないから 涙は
It won't go to waste, so my tears
今ここ by my side 寄り添ってるとなり
right here by my side, snuggling close
はーい、ということで前半ノンストップで駆け抜けてきましたが、
Hi, so we've powered through the first half non-stop,
ご覧の通り 衣装チェンジしてます！
but as you can see, we've changed our outfits!
いや本当に一人ひとり個性めちゃくちゃ主張されていて素敵。
Man, everyone's individual personalities really stand out, so wonderful.
ニコたんわ、かっこいいし、
Niko-tan is stylish,
すずちゃんね、りっちゃんわ、
Suzu-chan gives off that cozy, homely vibe.
もう過去かわいいし、すずちゃんわもう、可愛すぎるし！
And Suzu-chan is just way too cute!
それに、いすただって、りびたん、
And Istad, Rivi-tan,
え？え？可愛いね！
Huh? Huh? So cute!
なにその言い方！
What's with that way of saying it!
りっちゃんも可愛いニコちゃんも可愛い！
Ritchan is cute, Niko-chan is cute!
みんなに言ってる！みんなに言ってる！
You're saying that to everyone! To everyone!
ノートをそーね、ここで押す、嬉しいお知らせがあります！
We have a happy announcement right here!
なんと、このフローグロウの3Dお披露目ライブ、なんとXのトレンドで1位を獲得しました！
Guess what? This FLOW GLOW 3D reveal live hit #1 on X's trending topics!
やったー！
Yay!
それじゃあ、ここまできたら振り返っていきたいと思います！
Well then, with that said, let's look back on what we've done so far!
え、まずは男好き利央那がダリアとアップビートのメドレーを披露させていただきました！
First, Osugi Riona performed a medley of "Dahlia" and "Upbeat"!
させていただいたじゃないですよ
Wait, you weren't "allowed to", you did it!
いやもっとオブラートに包んでえろ出てたよ
No, you wrapped it in cellophane, you were so erotic!
ジャズダンスね、バレエとかの、ガるぞ披露させていただきました。セクシーだったかな、りおな？
You showed off jazz dance, ballet, and girl stuff. Was it sexy, Riona?
セクシーだったよ、りおな！どうだった？
It was sexy, Riona! How was it?
はーい、千早がトロンボーンとギターを自分で引きまして、
Hi, Chihaya played the trombone and guitar herself,
ギターの弾き語りで、欲求に満ちた青年団を歌わせていただきました！
and sang "Seienden Full of Desires" with acoustic guitar!
ちゃんとね練習してきたのでみんなに披露できて嬉しいです。聞いてくれてありがとう！
I practiced hard, so I'm happy to show it to everyone. Thanks for listening!
そして、ビビわですねメイクを生かした、鏡という楽曲を歌わせていただきました！
And Bibi sang "Kagami", a song that brings out her makeup!
メイクの変化見てくれたかな？可愛かった！
Did you notice the makeup change? It was cute!
お尻見たほうがいいよ
You should look at her butt!
お尻はダメだよ！やめて！
The butt is no good! Stop it!
はい、そして次いてわ、
Yes, and next up is,
ニコちゃんの大好きなバンポブチキンさんの青の昨日を、実はギターパパです！実パパです！
Niko-chan's favorite Bump of Chicken's "Blue Days", actually, it's guitar papa! Real papa!
そうなんです、ニコちゃんのいろんな思いを込めて歌わせていただいたので、また赤い服とか見てもらえたら嬉しいです。
That's right, I sang it with all of Niko-chan's feelings packed in, so I'd be happy if you check out the red clothes too.
はい、すが一サラシニアとギャルのメドレーを踊らせていただきました！
Yes, next up, we danced to a medley of Sarasini and Gal!
いや結構ね、かっこよく踊ったんだよ。楽しんでくれた？
Man, we danced pretty coolly. Did you enjoy it?
3メートルあったわ
It was 3 meters!
今は？今は？
Now? Now?
やっぱ3メートルあるわ。ちゃんと近くに来て見れるようにジャンプしてたりするんだよ。
As expected, it's 3 meters. We jumped so you could come close and see us.
はい、みんなのねソロを楽しんでもらった後は、私たちの新曲、そしてライブのタイトルにもなっております、MAKE IT, BREAK ITを初披露させていただきました！
Yes, after enjoying everyone's solos, we premiered our new song which is also the live's title, "MAKE IT, BREAK IT"!
今日リリース、あ、これはだめだ。はい、ということで、ラストスパート行きましょー！
Released today—ah, that's no good. Hi, with that, let's go into the final sprint!
その後は、私たちがこの間出させていただいたシングル「stay by my side」を披露させていただきました！
After that, we performed our single "stay by my side" that we released recently!
そして、ここで配信を見てくれているみんなにお知らせがあります！
And we have an announcement for everyone watching the stream right now!
なんだ、なんだ、なになに？
What is it, what is it?
お知らせは私たちと同じ5つあるので、1人ずつ紹介させていただきたいと思います！
The announcements are 5 just like us, so we'd like to introduce them one by one!
いいね。トップバッターはビビ、よろしく！
Nice. Top batter is Bibi, please!
はい、はい！それではこちらの覧ください、どうぞ！
Hi, hi! Then please take a look at this, go ahead!
ファーストアルバム「FLOW GLOW」についてです。発売来年1月21日！デビュー曲「FG ROADSTER」のほか、KIEのサウンドクリエイター陣が手掛ける全9曲を収録しています！
Regarding the 1st album "FLOW GLOW". Release date: January 21 next year! In addition to the debut song "FG ROADSTER", it includes a total of 9 songs crafted by KIE's sound creators!
通常盤はAタイプ、Bタイプあり、公式EC盤と全国流通盤では特典内容も違います。まあ、皆さんこの際どちらもゲットしちゃってください！
Regular editions come in Type A and Type B, and the bonus contents differ between the official EC edition and nationwide distribution edition. Well everyone, please grab both on this occasion!
そして、冒頭にも言った重大発表がこちら！
And the major announcement we mentioned at the beginning is this!
アルバムのリード曲になっている「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」について続報があります！先ほど初披露した6thシングル「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」のデジタルリリースが決定しました！
There's an update regarding "MAKE IT, BREAK IT", the lead song of the album! The digital release of the 6th single "MAKE IT, BREAK IT" which we premiered earlier has been decided!
デジタルリリースは明日11月24日です！
The digital release is tomorrow, November 24!
みんな絶対チェックしてよ！絶対聞いてね！
Everyone definitely check it out! Be sure to listen!
そして、この「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」のMVの公開なんですが、普段だったら楽曲のリリースとほぼ同時に公開やねんけど、運営さんがもっともっといいものにしたいということで公開を延期することになりました！
And regarding the release of the MV for "MAKE IT, BREAK IT", normally it's released almost simultaneously with the song, but management wanted to make it even better, so the release has been postponed!
私たちが登場します!
We are making our entrance!
さあ、みなさんどんな内容に仕上がっているか、今からめっちゃ楽しみにしててね！
Now everyone, look forward to what kind of content we've got prepared!
いや、かっこよく踊ったもんね
Man, we danced so cool!
そう、ダンスとかもね、やったもんね。ダンスね、やりましたよ、はい。
Yeah, we did dances and stuff too. We really did it, yeah.
続いてはチハ、お願いします!
Next up is Chiha, please!
はい、それではこちらをご覧ください、どうぞ!
Alright, please take a look at this, go ahead!
ホロカについてです。一昨日発売されたチハとニコのスターターデッキ、実は今日のライブでお披露目した新章のセカンドカードが収録されているんです!
It's about Holoca. The starter decks for Chiha and Nico released the day before yesterday actually include the second-chapter cards unveiled at today's live!
みんなにはね、サプライズのつもりで先行してセカンド衣装を入れてもらったんですが、びっくりしましたか?
We had them include the second outfits in advance as a surprise for everyone. Were you surprised?
バリチャップね、実はね、出てたんだよね、ははっ
It was actually already out, haha.
ええ、これら二つのスターターデッキは取り扱いのあるカードショップにて販売中です。気になった方はぜひ手にとってみてください。
These two starter decks are currently on sale at participating card shops. If you're interested, please check them out.
ホロカに関する情報はまだまだあります! こちらもご覧ください、どうぞ!
There's still more information about Holoca! Please take a look at this too, go ahead!
来月19日発売の新ブースターパック「アヤカシヴァーミリオン」、その中に今日りっちゃんがお披露目した新章のセカンドが収録されています!
In the new booster pack 'Ayakashi Vermilion' releasing on the 19th of next month, the second-chapter cards Ritchan unveiled today are included!
うっそマジ? なんだよそれ!
No way, seriously? What's that!
えーちょっといいね、スターフさーん
Eh, that's pretty nice, Staff-san—
ビビとスーンちゃんのもはやこうね、お願いしますよ
Bibisun and Soon-chan's too, please come on.
ビビね、やってやってください。うるさいんですが、うちの子らがすいません
Bibi, go ahead and do it. Sorry about our kids being so noisy.
ね、楽しみですね。
Right, looking forward to it.
はい、では続いてはスーンちゃんお願いします!
Alright, next is Soon-chan, please!
はい!ホロライブ公式ぬいぐるみブランド「ホロライブプロダクトフレンドwithU」、通称ホロフレ! ついに私たちフローグローの国々が登場します!
Yes! The official Hololive plushie brand 'Hololive friends with u', aka Holofre! Finally, our Flow Glow plushies are making their appearance!
やったー！去年のEXPOで開発中とお知らせしてしてからやっと皆さんにお届けできるようになりました!
Yay! Ever since we announced they were in development at last year's EXPO, we can finally deliver them to everyone!
注目は髪型や衣装、とにかく再現度がすごーい! 今日の22時より予約開始となりますのでお見逃しなく!
The highlight is the hair and outfits, the level of recreation is amazing! Pre-orders start tonight at 22:00, so don't miss it!
続いてのグッズはこちら!
The next merch is this!
今回お披露目した3Dの姿がアクリルスタンドになります! 先輩たちの3Dアクスタを持ってる人なら分かると思うんですが、かなり大きめのサイズとなっております。
The 3D appearances we unveiled today will become acrylic stands! If you have the seniors' 3D acrylic stands, you probably know, but they are quite large.
存在感ばっちりな私たちの3Dアクスタ、ぜひ手にとってください! こちらもホロフレと同じ今日の22時より予約開始となりますので合わせてチェックしてくれると嬉しいです!
With a great presence, please grab our 3D acrylic stands! Just like Holofre, pre-orders start tonight at 22:00, so we'd be happy if you check both!
続いてはニコ、お願いします!
Next is Nico, please!
はーい! 池袋にある、まずこちらをご覧ください、どうぞ!
Haaai! First, please take a look at this in Ikebukuro, go ahead!
池袋にある、池袋にあるTOWER RECORDS渋谷、サンシャインシティアルパ店ほか全国のTOWER RECORDS 12店舗にて、FLOW GLOW 1stアルバム発売を記念したポップアップの開催が決定!
At 12 TOWER RECORDS stores nationwide, including TOWER RECORDS Shibuya and Sunshine City Alpa in Ikebukuro, a pop-up shop commemorating the release of the FLOW GLOW 1st album has been decided!
今まで公式オンラインでしか手に入らなかったミックステープの1, 2のほか、先ほど紹介したフジのホロフレ、グッズも盛りだくさんの中に入ります!
In addition to mixtapes 1 and 2, which were previously only available on the official online store, it will be packed with goodies like the Fuji Holofre introduced earlier!
またですね、期間中にグッズをお買い上げの方にはノベルティももらえる予定となっておりますので、期間が1月20日から2月8日まで、グッズに関する詳しい情報やノベルティ条件などについては12月中旬開設予定の特設ページをご覧ください!
Also, those who purchase goods during the period are scheduled to receive novelty items, so from January 20th to February 8th, please check the special page scheduled to open in mid-December for detailed information on goods and novelty conditions!
おねがいします。
Please.
最後はりな、お願いします。
Lastly is Rina, please.
それではこちらをご覧ください、どうぞ!
Now please take a look at this, go ahead!
このあと、FLOW GLOW公式チャンネルのメンバーシップにてアフタートークライブがあります! そちらにも足を運びたいなというそこのあなた、ぜひ今のうちにメンバーシップの登録をお願いします!
After this, there's an after-talk live on the FLOW GLOW official channel's membership! To you who wants to go there too, please register for the membership right now!
そのアフタートークライブはここではなく別のステージからお届けします! そこ分でしか聞けないライブの裏話とか、あとはファーストアルバムに収録されている曲の中からあの曲を披露したいと思います!
That after-talk live will be delivered from a different stage, not here! I want to perform behind-the-scenes stories of the live that you can only hear there, and that song from the first album!
どう? ますます気になってきたんじゃない? 気になる! 気になる! 待ってるからね!
How's that? Aren't you getting more and more curious? Curious! Curious! We'll be waiting!
また、私たち一人一人のチャンネルのメンバーシップでも押しカメラ配信もあります! ぜひそちらも覗きに来てね!
Also, there are push-camera streams on each of our channel memberships! Please come take a peek at those too!
そして12月9日からの定期配信は3Dとなります!
And regular streams starting December 9th will be in 3D!
やったー！お楽しみにね!
Yay! Look forward to it!
さて皆さん、楽しい時間はあっという間ですね。そろそろライブも終了となります。
Well everyone, fun times fly by so fast. The live is soon coming to an end.
おかしいぞ、誰もツッコまない。ステージの裏でね、写真に写り込んでるんですが
That's strange, nobody is talking back. Behind the stage, we were captured in photos, but—
写真に写り込んでるんですけど、ごめんね、お疲れ様です
We were in the photo, sorry about that, good work.
とらとらとら...写真撮ろうね。映ってる? 写ってるよ。じゃいくよ。
Tora tora tora... Let's take a picture. Are we in it? We're in it. Here we go.
はい、チーズ! ポシャポシャポシャ...撮れた? みんな撮ったかな?
Ready, cheese! Poshaposhaposha... Did it take? Did everyone take it?
よし、ありがとう!
Alright, thank you!
スーンちゃんのおかげでね、素敵な思い出も撮れたところで、ここでメンバー一人一人からファンの皆さんにメッセージをお届けしたいと思います。まずはスーンちゃんから。
Thanks to Soon-chan, we got to capture wonderful memories, and now we'd like to deliver messages from each member to all the fans. First, from Soon-chan.
はい、フローグロー、そしてフローミーここまで一緒に走ってきてくれてありがとうございます! みんなのおかげで3Dになれたよ! こっから先もいろんな思い出をみんなと一緒に作っていきたいです。よろしくお願いします! 次はビビ!
Yes, Flow Glow, and Flow Me, thank you so much for running alongside us this far! Thanks to everyone, we were able to become 3D! From here on out, I want to create various memories together with everyone. Thank you! Next is Bibi!
はい！
Hi!
いつも応援してくださるフロミの皆さん、そしてメンバーみんな、いつもありがとう！
To all of you from Hrome who always support us, and to all our members, thank you always!
みんながいるからここまで来れました。
We're here because you're all with us.
2周年目もみんなと一緒にどんどん階段登っていきましょう！
Let's climb up many more steps together in our second year!
これからもよろしくね！ほんまにありがとう！
Thank you so much from the bottom of our hearts!
さあ続きましてニコはどうですか？
Now, continuing on, how about Niko?
FG？
FG?
はい。
Yes.
出会ってくれてありがとう。
Thank you for having us.
ありがとう。お風呂の皆さん、こちらもありがとうございます。
Thank you, everyone.
フログロというダイヤモンドに気付けたあなた、
You who noticed a diamond like Flow Glow...
天才じゃ！
are a genius!
これからも応援しよう、フロウ。ありがとう！
Thank you for continuing to support Flow Glow!
はい、じゃあありがとうございます。
Hi, thank you so much.
最後まで見ていただいてありがとうございます。
Thank you so much for watching until the very end.
今日は本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much today!
握手券も待ってます。
We're waiting for you at the handshake events too.
待ってるよ。
We'll be waiting.
はい、最後りっちゃん！
And finally, Ritchan!
デビュー当初からずっと夢だった歌って踊る姿をお届け、届けできたことを本当に嬉しく思います。ここまで応援してくださって本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you so much for supporting us all the way from our debut!
そしてね、
And...
みんなこれからもよろしくね！よろしくお願いします！
Thank you everyone so much, let's keep going!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ぴーぴー！大好きやで、チュー。
Woo-hoo! We love you!
本当にありがとう。
Really, thank you.
なんなんそれ？
What is that?
ありがとう、んまっ。
Thank you! Muah!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
フロウィー、アコールありがとう！
F-R-O-G-L-O-W, thank you!
今日は最高のライブでした！
Today was a super fun live!
みんな楽しんでくれたかな？
Did everyone enjoy it?
FGロードスター！
FG Roadster!
搭載V8エンジン
Carrying a V8 engine,
第7感持ってる原人
With the 7th sense original man,
6するこの世界と全人類
6-way changing world and all humanity,
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
We 5 changing the game,
轟く4輪発射セヨ
Burning 4 wheels, launching,
皆3キュースランヘヨ
Thank you all 3-fold, saranghae yo,
操る2台のturntable
Controlling 2 turntables,
獲る1番ここground 0
Taking #1 right here, ground zero!
(aye) リスク超えて挑戦
(Ayl) Going beyond risks, challenge,
チャンスもセットだ当然
Chances are set too, of course,
登り上げる頂点
Climbing up to the peak,
座布団積んでく笑点
Laughter built up like cushions,
乗り込むFG ROADSTER
Riding in the FG Roadster,
特殊部隊集合能力者
Special unit gathered, espers,
この歴史に名を彫る彫刻家
Carving our names in history,
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
Lock on!
目と目が合えば I know
Eyes lock and I know...
キミこそが相棒
You're the only partner for me.
メロつかせる才能 (What?)
Talent that weaves melodies (What?)
パッと見天使でも、中には潜むデーモン
An angel at a glance, but a demon deep inside.
so ギャップと愛嬌あれば最強
So with a gap and affection, it's unbeatable.
Haterはシカト
Haters are ignored.
「へぇ、あっそ！」
"Hah, is that so?"
一蓮托生オーガナイズ 退屈に用はない
A unified organization with no use for boredom.
一本線描くボーダーライン 届かない？しゅーがない
Drawing the boundary line, can't you reach it? Too bad.
ウチらが集まればバリ baddest
When we gather, we're the baddest.
見惚れちゃうでしょ？
Aren't you captivated?
Look at me, look at me now...
置いてかない絶対
Never leaving you behind, absolute.
ついて来れ 5 MC's
Follow the 5 MCs.
本気のフライデーナイト
Our serious flight-day night.
Make it? Break it?
Make a revolution
アタシを貫き傾け
Pierce and lean into yourself.
夢に強引 going, going on!
Going, going on with strong impulse!
Break through and never stop 真ん中突き抜け行け
Break through and never stop, break right through!
Can't get enough
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
ほら、どっちにするの？
Well, which will it be?
有形無形沸かす Flow Glow
Stirring up imagination, Flow Glow.
ay 口先より行動 if you wanna be マイメン
Actions speak louder than words, if you wanna be my men.
よそ見とかナシで warning! 没収ほら没収
Look away? Not a chance. Warning, confiscation!
味わいなくって burning! もっと hotter もっと hotter
Taste it, burning! More hotter, more hotter.
ハイになりなくって
Getting high!
置いてかない絶対
Never leaving you behind, absolute.
ついて来れ 5 MC's
Follow the 5 MCs.
本気のフライデーナイト
Our serious flight-day night.
Make it? Break it?
Brand new generation
感じるままアガれアガれ
Just as you feel it, raise it up, raise it up!
華麗に降臨 only, only one
Gleaming brilliantly, only, only one.
退屈な neverland 速攻で抜け出せ i say
A boring Neverland, break out with a blitz.
Ready or not?
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
朝まで make some noise
Make some noise until the morning.
Make a revolution
アタシを貫き傾け
Pierce and lean into yourself.
夢に強引 going, going on!
Going, going on with strong impulse!
Break through and never stop 真ん中突き抜け行け
Break through and never stop, break right through!
Can't get enough
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
ほら、どっちにするの？
Well, which will it be?
cornered せめてもて切りギリ
Hey, cornered, at least cut it short.
motor 全開自費 biggie
Motor fully engaged, big beeps.
ソナーから導き wide お幅がびじびじ
Guided from the sonar, wide differences.
ダイヤ焦がしてドナッツ
Diamonds falling, donats.
弾け飛んでくドラム缶
Flying apart, drum cans.
顧客満足度高くてぶち上がってる若者さん
Customer satisfaction is high and rising, young folks.
ゼロから最高到達点 溜まってる体力亢進
Zero to the highest point, filled-up stamina.
打破するこの超新星 覚醒突入ボーナス day
Spurring on this newborn star, awakening, and breaking through.
一直線伸びてるダノ vipr vibration エンジンのカバー
Stretching straight, the vipr vibration engine cover.
速度増し仕上がってるクド 限界重力にがひょいよ
Speed finished, the gravity limit gravity.
開拓しなくってフランジア 旅立ちのローダスター only one
Not exploring, running free, the only one.
アクセル踏み込んでくドンピシャ
Stepping on the accelerator, dead on target.
飛んでくニッポンいざ
Fly, Japan, let's go!
いつも配るキの終点
Always handing out the destination.
風のホテルが休憩所 並んでそこ UFO
The hotel wind takes a break, lined up there, UFO.
降り立つチュー ステーション
Station where two tracks cross.
物語の継承 hey まるで 900s
Story's legacy, hey, just like the 900s.
この先何世紀も成長 生き延びて結果達成
This past century too, growing, surviving, and succeeding.
Can't get enough
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
朝まで make some noise
Make some noise until the morning.
Make a revolution
アタシを貫き傾け
Pierce and lean into yourself.
夢に強引 going, going on!
Going, going on with strong impulse!
Break through and never stop 真ん中突き抜け行け
Break through and never stop, break right through!
Can't get enough
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it? Break it?
ほら、どっちにするの？
Well, which will it be?
以上私たち、FLOW GLOWでした！
That's us, Flow Glow!
you'll see! make it or break it!